Every day at a minute past midnight the sci-fi adventure begins... again.
12:01 is a science fiction, thriller, tv movie film directed by Jack Sholder.
Office employee Barry Thomas is caught in a "time bounce"
caused by a glitch in the company's secret project.
Now the same day occurs again and again - and Barry's the only one who can do anything about
it, including saving the life of beautiful research assistant Lisa Fredericks.
Barry Thomas, played by Jonathan Silverman.
Lisa Fredericks, played by Helen Slater.
Dr. Thadius Moxley, played by Martin Landau.
Robert Denk, played by Nicolas Surovy.
Anne Jackson, played by Robin Bartlett.
Howard Richter, played by Jeremy Piven.
12:01 is a 1993 American science fiction television film directed by Jack Sholder and
starring Jonathan Silverman, Helen Slater, Jeremy Piven, and Martin Landau.
It originally aired on the Fox Network in the United States on July 5, 1993.
It is an adaptation of Richard Lupoff's short story "12:01 P.M.," published in the
December 1973 issue of The Magazine of Fantasy & Science Fiction.
The story had previously been adapted into the 1990 short
film 12:01 PM starring Kurtwood Smith.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.